听力材料一：听对话，选出正确的图画。
what's the weather like in Inchuan?
Oh, it's windy.
Bob, what's the weather like in Inchuan?
Text 2. What are you doing, Mike?
I'm watching a basketball match.
It will end at 9 o
What are you doing, Mike?
I'm watching a basketball match.
It will end at 9 o
Text 3. Why do you like pandas best?
Because they are cute and friendly.
Why do you like pandas best?
Text 4. What would you like to drink?
Coffee, please. What would you like to drink?
Coffee, please. Text 5.
Bill, drive carefully.
is a school ahead.
Sorry, I didn't see the sign.
Bill, drive carefully.
There is a ahead.
听对话及对话后的问题，然后选择正确答案
Text 6. How often do you go to the library?
I go to the library once a week.
Question. How often does the man go to the library?
How often do you go to the library?
I go to the library once a week.
Question. How often does the man go to the library?
Text 7. What do you want to be when you grow up?
My parents want me to be a teacher, but I hope to become a policeman.
Question. What does the boy want to be?
What do you want to be when you grow up?
My parents want me to be a teacher, but I hope to become a policeman.
Question. What does the boy want to be?
Text 8. you going to the Great Wall or Tiananmen Square?
Both, but I'll go to visit Tiananmen Square first.
Question. Which place is the boy going to visit first?
Are you going to visit the Great Wall or Tiananmen Square?
Both, but I'll go to visit Tiananmen Square first.
Which place is the boy going to visit first?
Text 9. You don't look well.
What's the matter, Tom?
I have a toothache.
Question. What's wrong with Tom?
You don't look well.
What's the matter, Tom?
I have a toothache.
Question. What's wrong with Tom?
Text 10. What can I do for you,
I want to buy a pair of for my son.
Question. Where are they talking?
What can I do for you, sir?
I want to buy a of for my son.
Question. are Text 11.
三，听对话，选择正确答案。
听下面一段对话，回答第十一、十二小题。
Excuse me. Could you show me the way to the post office?
Certainly. Just go along Green Street and turn left at the first crossing.
Then go down Bridge Street.
You will see the post office is next to the bookstore.
Is it far from here?
No. It's about two kilometers from here.
You can take a bus or walk there.
Okay. I'll walk there.
Thank you very much.
Text 11. Excuse me.
Could you show me the way to the post office?
Certainly. Just go along Green Street and turn left at the first crossing.
Then go down Bridge Street.
You will see the post office is next to the bookstore.
Is it far from here?
No. It's about two kilometers from here.
You can take a bus or walk there.
Okay. I'll walk there.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.
听下面一段对话，回答第十三至十五小题。
Text 12. Tony, what kind of music do you like best?
I like many kinds of music.
And I like country music best of all.
Oh. There will be a concert this afternoon.
Would you like to go with me?
Sure. I'd love to.
When shall we meet then?
At a quarter past three.
Okay. Where shall we meet?
At the gate of the music hall.
Okay. See you then.
See you. Tony, what kind of music do you like best?
I like many kinds of music.
And I like country music best of all.
Oh. There will be a concert this afternoon.
Would you like to go with me?
Sure. I'd love to.
When shall we meet then?
At a quarter past three.
Okay. Where shall we meet?
At the gate of the music hall.
Okay. See you then.
See you. Text 13 Hello boys and girls.
四、听力，听短文，然后根据表格提示和所听内容完成下列各小题，每空
一词。
Here is some information about our volunteer activities.
We will go to the old people's home on October 2nd.
It is not far from our school.
So we can go there by bike.
The old people there have no family members, so they are very lonely.
We can read a newspaper to them or just listen to them.
We can also clean their clothes and make dinner for them.
If you want to more information about it, you can call Mr.
at 754 -8216.
Hello boys and girls.
Here is some information about our volunteer activities.
We will go to the old people's home on October 2nd.
It is not far from our school.
So we can go there by bike.
The old people there have no family members, so they are very lonely.
We can read a newspaper to them or just listen to them.
We can also clean their clothes and make dinner for them.
If you want to more information about you can call Mr.
Wong at 754 -8216.